INFO

Full Name: Juan Carlos Moreno Munevar

Phone: 517 2440

Phone Mobile: 321 343 9369 e-mail: jcmm.info@gmail.com

Git page: https://ju4nmoreno.github.io/jcmm/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/juan-moreno-frontend

SUMMARY

Front-End Developer, with knowledge in HTML, CSS and JavaScript with outstanding experience developing standards-compliant & browsers compatible websites and applications in deadline-oriented environments. With 4 + years of experience related to development of solutions web, High Skills for organization and planning of interactive projects. Like a Professional Graphic Designer, I have the capability to integrate the usability and design giving a holistic approach to my work.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

OSG June 2011 - Currently

Interactive Web Developer

Web Sites Development with the following specialties

 knowledge in: html (pug.js), css (sass, less),

JavaScript (Pattern design, Es6, angular, three.js).

- Experience building responsive websites.
- Automation: grunt, gulp, node.js scripts.
- CSS processors (Less, SASS).
- Cross-browser compatibility.

Freelance August 2011 – June 2013

FrontEnd

Sites Development with the following specialties:

• knowledge in: HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

- Experience building responsive websites.
- CSS processors (Less, SASS).
- Cross-browser compatibility.

Mccann March 2010 – June 2011

Interactive Web Designer / Interactive Web Developer

Designer and Web Sites Development with the following specialties:

- Strong knowledge of creating and designing an interactive experience across multiple digital platforms.
- knowledge in: HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Strong working experience with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects and image optimization for web.

Digiway January 2008 – February 2010

Designer and Web Sites Development with the following specialties

- Strong knowledge of creating and designing an interactive experience across multiple digital platforms.
- Experience with development with scripting languages: HTML, CSS and action script 3.
- Strong working experience with Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects and image optimization for web.

EDUCATION

Jorge Tadeo Lozano University - Graphic Designer, Bogota — Colombia 1999 - 2005